restodb.com 2010-12-22

# Privacy Policy - Restaurant and Dining Guide - Directory, Review, Articles, Photos

RestoDB is a website that provides a community for restaurant lovers. You can join this community by becoming a member. This will require RestoDB to collect personal information from each member. This personal information includes:

  * First name
  * Last name
  * E-mail address
  * Gender
  * Age
  * Location
  * Mailing address
  * Phone number
  * Mobile number
  * Occupation
  * Favorite food/restaurant
  * Photos

If you prefer, you can surf anonymously at RestoDB website and you don’t need to provide any personal information. Though there are a lot of advantages provided by RestoDB if you become our members. This information can be found in RestoDB Member Reward Programs.

Each time you login, RestoDB will only show your username and will not expose any other personal information on the website. Some personal information such as member’s full name and e-mail address will be used when member invites friends or other visitors via e-mail to become RestoDB members. Other personal information submitted by member will be used for the purpose of ‘Member Award Programs’. Such personal information may be shared to particular restaurant for the purpose of identification in case you win an award/redeem the points you collect while surfing and becoming an active member.

Other than both activities mentioned above, member’s personal information will not be shared with or displayed to any other person. 

As RestoDB member, you may at anytime update, modify or remove the information you have submitted to us. You may also at anytime cancel your account by emailing to us and request for cancellation of your account.

RestoDB use cookies to save username and session validations. However, we do not use cookies to collect any personal information from members. We also collect information that is not personal identifiable, such as browser type and IP address. 

Each RestoDB member account will be password-protected. RestoDB uses industry standard security measures to protect all information that is stored at RestoDB servers and database. Although we make good efforts to secure all information and ensure the integrity and safety of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee full security to prevent third-party hackers from illegally obtaining this information. We limit access to members’ personal information to our employees, such as customer service personnel, to do their jobs. If you have any inquiries about our security, please contact us.

RestoDB website has links to other websites. This links may be placed by RestoDB (for advertisement) or by other RestoDB members. Please keep in mind that RestoDB is not responsible for the privacy policies of other website. We recommend all members and visitors of RestoDB website to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects your personal information.

RestoDB has the right to modify or update this policy from time to time. Any changes to this policy will be notified to you via e-mail or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

Latest Forum Posted

Ada yg bisa share gimana dapatin disc. card dari shangri-la hotel. bisa di ...

Latest Articles Posted

Bagi Kaum Pencinta Daging, Disediakan Aneka Menu Utama Dari Negeri 1001 Mal ...
